whether you're watching on YouTube or
listening as a podcast remember to
subscribe and hit the bell to track
upcoming releases so drop in then I look
forward to speaking with you both and
Sam as well who can't join us today as
much as I look forward to having any
conversation at all and that's that's a
strange thing because we've spoken a few
times for quite a long time each time
but I remember saying to Sam it sort of
feels a bit like coming home to me and
I'm not sure why that is I'm just very
appreciative of it and and we find
ourselves now recording this where
previously we hadn't been and where had
where this had been a group for us to
get together and drop in to communicate
well help each other think through
things explore reality even we now find
ourselves in a rather interesting time
time that's that threatened
apse of a few things and is full of
existential predicament as well as it's
full of opportunity and thank you for
being here and agreeing to record this
with me so that we might let in some
people on a kind of conversation that to
me feels vitalizing so yeah Mike and
Johnny it's lovely to be with you it's
great to be here yeah feels like we're
collectively in some uncharted waters
and I kind of feel like that on a micro
scale here in this conversation I'm not
really sure what what is going to arise
and you know the time that passes while
we're we're here together
but I feel either and and ready to
explore and navigate with with you guys
because I trust that you all are you
know like deeply caring and and your
heart is in the right place and so these
conversations are something I look
forward to as well so yeah delighted to
be here and and curious to see what what
kind of things arise over this next
little while mmm yeah likewise
and I I even I just as we were talking
before you hit record and that my heart
rate and pulse kind of started to slow
down as we were as we were talking I
felt myself just grounding slightly and
I think that for me these conversations
that we've had has been a way of
orienting and and kind of checking in
with with the compass and I do feel
somewhat somewhat ungrounded like as if
someone has just set fire to the map
that I thought I had and I'm looking
forward to seeing where this goes and
and seeing what questions are most alive
for us right now
mmm I think that's a beautiful place to
begin that question what questions are
alive for us most right now that's
something I've seen you post on Twitter
I think Johnny and there's been
something I've been in a few
conversations where that's being posed
so I'm actually going to I'm gonna throw
it at you both right now perhaps perhaps
Johnny what questions are alive for you
most right now I think there are the
rescue and and perhaps they're the one
that is above all of them is I feel ma
I'll pull potentially conflicting
emotions and questions that are
surfacing and allowing myself to be the
containment that holds all of them
whether that's there the fear and the
uncertainty and just concerned for my
loved ones and my family and and the
global situation which is then I kind of
juxtapose with this sense of almost like
this fire in my belly right it's like
this sense of purpose and weird
excitement that's almost like I imagine
someone might feel as they're about to
go into battle and it's just like
nervous anticipation and it's kind of
cooling for and sitting with both of
those at the same time I think is
interesting for me and and I think the
question that feels most alive on my
mind right now is is one that might
mentions just before we hit record which
is that question of what what is mine to
give how can I best serve in this place
now that I feel resource and I feel
centered and I feel like I'm I'm
supported and I'm fortunate to have all
of my my needs met what is a way that I
can express my gift and put myself
forward in this in this time and make my
make my contribution and and how can I
do that from a place that is
authentically from me
and not just responding or reacting to
the the kind of fire hose that is
appears to be going going online so
that's where that's what I'm really
sitting with and and the answers seem to
be changing in real time like every day
I wake up with a new a new sense so I'm
just learning to listen right now I'm
tuning in man that's a good question I
think this is something I pause is worth
taking for and for those of you
listening as well how can I serve we
might ask what is service because it's a
bit of a funny word it comes from I
believe that the Latin word serve us
which was comes from slave but that's
not quite how we use it and the
interesting thing is that when you talk
of serving something as almost like a
split there but the way I sort of think
about it is that
from the perspective of interconnection
a service is automatically service of
self and other and world that's its
highest form we are both master and
slave and neither and if you are both
then that sort of puts a bit of a twist
on it is perhaps more where can I lead
how can I make an offering what
invitation can I extend and follow
through on what can I offer to those
around me how can I be grounded in
myself
you mentioned this notion of tuning in
how can we tune in to know what is ours
to offer and then there's that whole
angle of well just what is required in
order to be stable enough resilient
enough to offer at all so there's some
initial things that come up for me yeah
part of my I agree with you Johnny and
how this is a very dynamic process
entertaining this question I feel like
my answer to it is changing as quickly
as the spirit of the moment you know
we're getting this firehose of news like
that it just feels like time is speeding
up in a way and slowing down in another
way given that we're pulled out of what
more commonly would be our distractions
the events we go to things like that but
it's been some of the things that I've
felt myself drawn to that might be
useful for people because some of them
have some universal I think application
one is just how am i doing and I ask
myself what is mine to do here and I
have to reflect and see how I'm doing
and it's all of it before I try to take
any additional action because I don't
want to similarly to what you're
describing I don't want to leave
into doing things from a place that is
unrooted in a way I want to be clear in
the action that I'm taking and I want to
there's a sense of urgency that I feel
but I don't want that urgency to tip in
to overwhelm to the point that I will
lose my sense of clarity and what I'm
doing and so there's tongues sometimes
it's meditation or it's going for a walk
when it isn't you know
pouring snow outside but there's also
the thing that has been driving a lot of
significance towards me as tending to
the social fabric around me checking in
with the people who I care about and
seeing how are they doing are they
making sense of all this in a way that's
gonna you know be supportive are they
taking it seriously
do they need someone to listen to them I
know how are they doing and just sending
out the signal that I'm here if you need
me and that feels really meaningful to
do it feels supremely meaningful for me
to be able to extend myself so if you
need somebody to talk to you to help you
know figure it figure things out what's
going on here whether it's personally or
just understanding what's happening you
know more globally I'm happy to extend
that and then there are other things
that are more kind of specific to what I
think feel like are my unique skill sets
in the position I'm in but those two
things at least feel very you know
applicable to most people in those
situations just checking in with
yourself and checking in with the others
around you so those those feel like good
answers that are in some ways
continuously flowing to me but it's
different what I need or who I feel
drawn to reach out to that keeps
shifting and changing
I feel like I've been spending the last
few days doing the same and mostly in
contact with friends and family and
there's discerned two-blade met maybe
that's enough
like maybe that doesn't need to be this
this grand gesture but this is I see
like I'm cycles and to be that mountain
amongst the hurricane for people who
need some need nangka and need some
foundation and the other piece that came
to me as as you were talking was that
sometimes I think that there is this
this desire to act and to do and to to
be of service can sometimes be a
distraction from sitting with what is
and I'm conscious of not kind of
bypassing and that's that's sinking into
the current situation and to the
feelings and almost using service as a
socially rewarded way of not looking at
what is actually coming up and yeah that
just feels interesting for me to think
about and it and perhaps where is that
desire to serve coming from and is it
service to something bigger something
that it's coming through me something
that is flowing through or is it my own
desires for validation and insecurities
there's also a piece I'm not saying
this is what's happening in your
experience but I'm sensing it out there
in the ethers this feeling of oh this is
a huge opportunity I'm like it's
unprecedented unlike anything you know
and there's a lot of truth to that and
if someone is even a little bit seduced
by like a hustlers mentality you know
you got a sees that you gotta like work
yourself to the bone and really take
advantage of this golden opportunity
then that they could prompt kind of
action that is more rooted in the places
that you're speaking about insecurity or
like like yeah it's just not it feels
like the compass isn't quite calibrated
or something it's it's pointed in a
direction that might not be the best
direction yeah I I think these are
extremely important considerations and
let me share a little bit about my state
regarding this because I feel absolutely
100% like now is the time to act I am
utterly clear about it and it's not
coming from that place of hustling it's
it's coming from well it's it's coming
from a few places the moment is now
right that's that there's no getting
away from that and I has hit the
fan okay but but the thing is is that it
already had you know it already had and
for a number of
many of the conversations I was having
many of the the the underlying the
underlying emotional current of who I
was if I was speaking truthfully in a
situation was
often if I really let that out it was
towards the way of prodding really of
dropping the dropping the space like
heightening the intensity because much
of what we're facing at the moment we
have been facing for quite some time and
the that the challenges we've had
individually and collectively in being
continuous in our connection in in a a
more positive feedback relationship a
more adaptive feedback relationship with
our ecology our world is one where there
have been many sleepy and dangerous
patterns that have been running for a
long time and through it all it's been
increasingly only more clear to me that
and you know it was it was Johnny it was
something you said earlier perhaps
before we started recording it's towards
this side of well what is the response
it's that process of tuning in what am i
returning to where can we go again from
how can we Kindle the that fire in
ourselves that is
that is of the same flame that is once a
remembering of a way to be with each
other
remembering the being mode believers
Erich Fromm has the term and Jambo Vicki
articulates so well a deep mode of
participation in reality with each other
in a mode of growth in a mode of
transformation that is the tuning of the
compass it seems to me that's been
called for and is only more more called
for now and the experience I have is
that if I wasn't to coordinate
conversations and I can't do much else
I'm more or less now quarantined in this
apartment and doing things on a local
level is not so clearly possible to me
I've thought of putting up a few notices
in the left and what Abbey but we've
just moved in here and it doesn't feel
much like a community but there is
something I can do online with a view to
with a view to taking this again back
into the local world in the future and
that is a coordinate to send out
invitations for people to show up and
engage with each other
that place of authenticity yes there's
that part of me that's still very very
interested in esoteric conversations
about what does initiation look like
what is what's the nature of meaning
what's the nature of spirituality
what's a framework of metaphysics by
which we can make sense of be in contact
with embody in this time but
fundamentally it is it's as simple as
being here now together and as long as I
place and allow myself demand of myself
as well it's I guess it's a voluntary
self obligation to place the being here
now with you first that is that is the
service and you know I'd invite you both
to consider that that is what you are
doing already and there has to be
primary two doubts we may have about a
sort of a constructed understanding of
well as is coming from a place maybe of
looking for validation and maybe part of
it is but there's again that process of
settling in and tuning in and there's
always the key it seems to me to those
questions
you
yeah ultimately validation is is part of
what drives an action to be taken and
yet someone in our circles deeply
benefits from that because they attended
a workshop that was hosted that where
they got to really feel seen and heard
or something like that does it really
matter as much you know it's like sure
it matters to some degree but I like the
kind of way you're speaking to their Tim
it's like we don't really need to worry
too much about the cleanliness of our
intentions if we're acting and there may
be is some part of us that feels
insecure and we need to get out there
and share something that is of value or
of worth to validate some kind of
identity we've been forming for
ourselves if that is that if that's part
of the the combustion that puts
something out to the world that does
make a meaningful difference on someone
then great and there's still those this
part of the process of self-revelation
and self-discovery as we take these
actions and then realize ah I did that a
little bit because there was a part of
me that didn't feel like I was doing
enough now or X Y or Z whatever the
narrative is and so yeah there's there's
been I'm not sure which one of you it
was may have been Johnny as' spoke of
like fire in the belly and you just
spoke to him like the time is now and I
there is something very catalytic about
this moment and I'm seeing it in so many
places this up surging of coordination
and people have a real tangible thing to
focus on and to and to work on together
and that is very very exciting to see
yeah it just inspires a great deal of
hope in me watching that unfold hmm
yeah and just to continue on that thread
my sense is that a lot of the a lot of
the conversations that we've all been
having for maybe the past kind of couple
of years they felt in some ways quite
heady and quiet intellectual and
potentially on and on an abstract level
or poor navigating hypothetical
challenges are going to be coming down
the line and what I think the source of
that fire for me has been this sense
that everything that we have been
anticipating and we have been talking
about and hypothesizing it seems like it
is now unfolding in real time and I
think the invitation is to take these
he's like these conversations from the
head to the heart and creating spaces
for for this this wisdom and this
collective knowledge to be embodied and
to be actually put out into the world
and and I and I think I share your sense
of urgency is the wrong word but it's
almost like a cooling forth and I think
if I was to if I was that articulate how
I would describe my my project up until
this point it's it's almost been like a
pushing it's like I think this is needed
so I'm kind of pushing my my
conversations out there and it feels now
like there is this this pull and there
is this like it's like the magnetic
field has switched and we're now being
drawn into this this this fire and this
you know this Candis deep uncertainty
and that is it's it's it's almost
intoxicating in a way and it because it
is such an intense feeling I think that
is where my my you know my mistrust is
it's coming from which it's like this
feels so alive in the ends and as you
were talking about validation
I wonder if another way of framing
validation might be just to say that we
desire our gifts to be seen we want to
be seen in the world for what we were we
shared what we create
and when it's framed like that that
feels to me like you know that feels
right and I think that's what we all
desire on some level and it's it feels
like a very human very human desire can
I put this to you guys and I think that
was a beautifully articulated Johnny by
the way but can I can I put something to
you it's something that I feel quite
strongly and I don't want to say it as
though I'm saying hey this is how it is
and so I'm wary of blind spots here the
experience I have I think not
my motivation while while I have in the
most on so logic
salient fundamental non-negotiable
experience in my life experiences in my
life found that an affirmation of life
in the form of an appreciation for the
possibility of life to further that
potential to be at all manifest in the
word love I think while I found that to
be that flame
perhaps maybe just as strong or perhaps
not just as strong but that's something
I feel motivate me so strongly in
perhaps it's been more salient in the
last few weeks has been has been a
certain kind of fear and fear I think is
a nice we can think of as a compass when
read correctly points back to love
points towards love and in saying that
I'm influenced by a few few
conversations in my life and also
recently reading some wonderful words by
a philosopher and brilliant thinker
named Forrest Landry who I hope to be
talking to soon and we'll share some
words of I think in a company went with
this conversation because I think they
are so important but it's fear I
experience when it comes to taking
action and why I'm feel so motivated
right now and again I would ask our
listeners to tune into and and see if
this fits for them is that if after all
this work I've done
Trinity to a coordinate having the
opportunity to share that which has for
me being vitalizing in my life if I did
not share if I did not show up to bring
forth whatever it is that comes out at
me out of me
anchored from that place when I have
been to certain depths struggled deeply
with with certain things if I was to not
step forward not continue to it would be
tantamount to a lie for me it would be
refusing a call and the the notion of
living a lie of refusing to be who you
are to be I I I just I will not live
that way I am terrified of finding a
moment with myself when perhaps with you
a loving partner there is an opportunity
to embrace in a hug in a moment of
crisis I'm terrified of the thought
unity for you to act from that place and
you didn't and and so I get a lot of
motivation from that that raises the
word vigilance for me
and it inspires a greater sense of
choice in my moment-to-moment
interactions there's a way that we can
sort of allow our prevailing
conditioning to just go on and on and on
as is and be very forgiving with
ourselves for that which is not a bad
thing but the yeah there is something
haunting about what you just described
there Tim this sense of there was a
choice I could have made to protect or
elevate or secure something of
immeasurable value and I'd drop the ball
mm-hmm it's a devastating feeling to
really you know entertained that
possibility or even reflect on moments
in the past where I may have done that
if I really consider myself if I really
feel into the the truth of the capacity
that I feel that I have in my heart
knowing there have been many times where
I was sort of I haven't measured up and
it's okay but that only adds to the
inspiration I still have a chance today
I still have the opportunity to show up
today and and live in truth so as you
were as you remember sharing that Tim I
I felt pretty emotional to be honest I
felt like a deep yeah just a deep
feeling in my gut and be the image that
comes to mind for me is one of a like a
ripening fruit and I think there is this
sense that we have been ripening in
certain ways and that if we weren't to
allow us those two to fall from a tree
and to be eaten there is the sense that
of like rotting on the vine of like that
that creative energy almost
metastasizing and and turning into a
kind of destructive force if it is not
channeled and used in an appropriate way
and everything that you said felt deeply
true for me yeah and it's actually
brought a huge amount of clarity to my
my current situation so thank you yeah
both of you always hit home for me Mike
Mike that's um that's quite a thing to
presence to really draw into presence
those times you've dropped the ball
previously and of course we all have
then there's part of me that's like you
know what this is a very serious
situation we're in very serious and this
trigger of covert 19 it is you know it's
it's it's tossing us a different kind of
ball I think you know and I've I've
never had the opportunity to drop a ball
like this do everything so maybe maybe
maybe that's something that could help
stave off some of that frustration for
previous times but you're right in that
that our past is there to be learned
from and to be to to to to
inspiration in in the present hmm and
maybe my my the thrust and the the drive
to catch this unique sort of ball is
informed by the the recognised pain of
how like what happens you know the other
balls that I've dropped in some ways
were test cases preparing me for this
this climactic moment in the the plot of
our lives in the way had you know sort
of forged a certain degree of not armor
that's not quite right word but capacity
that endowed me with an ability to show
up whereas I might not have been able to
in this way in the past I see that as
well
Johnny can I can I ask you some
questions because I think those of us
who's listening and watching right now I
feel I feel they're with us here and
much of what we've spoken about is how -
well we've I can't encapsulate it all
about how to relate find out a
centeredness a groundedness in the chaos
around us
- to be attentive to be vigilant to
discern when the Bulls coming away and a
lot of people right now are I think
experiencing chaos and the bursting of a
bubble that they might have been living
in or perhaps they know someone who was
and where do you find
self when something so important and
stabilizing and like the very pillars of
your life when they're abruptly
disturbed and taken from you what is
what is the experience like of coming
out of that it's something that I have
been I've been reflecting on for the
last few days this sense of to me in
many ways I think the lasts its two and
a half years has has felt like that and
I feel like I've I finally reached this
place of um not solid ground but the
ground that I can really stand on and
it's reflecting back to that time when I
I lost my partner and it did feel like
in the space of two days everything that
I thought was going to happen in the
future just self combusted and
[Music]
everything I thought that was important
no longer seems to be and my entire
perspective was just was completely
shifted in such a short space of time
and as some of my reflections from that
process one of them for sure was the was
having to let go almost being forced to
let go of the illusion of being
self-reliance and independence and this
this identity that I cultivated of being
able to do everything on my own
I became abundantly clear that
I needed it other people and I needed to
be vulnerable enough to to ask sure
support and that in itself was a was a
huge learning and I assure me it feels
like it's a it's a - well there's two
distinct parts to the the process I feel
the first is he's being grounded and
being still enough to just be present to
whatever is arising and in in a space of
grief often there are feelings of to me
there was anger there was there was
blame there was guilt and shame to some
extent and just being still enough to
acknowledge those was was was a it took
time it took time for me and I think
what really what allowed the energy to
move through was having friends hold
space for me for for sharing and for the
floods of floods of tears and for me
going going into the sea and allowing
the the cold of the ocean to kind of
just sink into my bones and I think all
of what all of these these rituals or
these these practice having comment is
there is a sense of surrendering
interview what is and that for me over a
period of time as the different kind of
shades or different aspects of grief rid
their head there was this constant
invitation to surrender and and and to
allow myself to be weak to the to the
energy and the emotion that was moving
through
and that feels to me very relevant to
what I think is happening right now I I
feel as if some of what is surfacing is
this this almost collective collective
shadow and potentially collective grief
that hasn't been recognized or looked at
and we found ways to whether it's
through our work or through other
distractions or through numbing in
certain ways we've just not looked at it
and this feels like a moment of like
being almost forced to stay inside and
to sit with what it is there whatever
however that arises in us and the
invitation is to is to surrender enter
it and I can see this going in in two
ways for some people the emotions will
surface and there will be reactions of
fear and panic and me the triggers will
just be amplified and for others there
will be that sense of of accepting and
surrendering and and healing and I feel
like both of those are going to happen
on a on a worldwide scale in the in the
coming months
that was quite the experience
to listen to so there is something
practical I would like to offer to both
of you and those who are listening or
watching and that is I and perhaps we if
you would would like to join me I'm
going to be hosting a series of ongoing
conversations on zoom with up to 20
people and with the intention of being
here now together so sharing in this
time so tuning in together it seems to
me to be a at least towards the
direction of a solution sounds too full
but something constructive and positive
insofar as moving that energy and
connecting with each other in a time of
otherwise physical isolation and the aim
is very much to hold that space and to
to hold a space in which the very
participation in it is a teacher that
lights that flame in whoever
present to then go and do the same thing
to gather their friends and family to
reach out to others and to connect to
really tune in and to express what comes
forth and so if you'd like to I'm going
to be coordinating these over the coming
over the coming weeks they'll definitely
be one next Thursday and otherwise I'd
like to be yeah that's that's it really
yeah I'm I mean
yeah it's not even not even a question
yeah god yeah I mean people it it's it's
it's just it's just very clear to me and
it's something I've been hit me a lot in
some of the conversations I've had over
the last few days there's there's a
there is a there is a privilege of being
here with you guys and and so much of
what the wisdom seems to be is is in the
invitation to participate and so it
seems to me they're appropriate
outgrowth of of being here now with you
to invite to invite people to
participate in that so
well I I've got some people as well that
I'd also like to introduce you to Johnny
you've mentioned that you've been
interested to gather together elders and
I hope I'm not you know jumping the gun
here in any way but I hope you do that
you know I would like to listen you know
and there's some people I'd like to put
you in touch with in that way there's a
man named guy sing stock who you might
have come across he's the founder of
circling and I think you guys would have
a really nice resonance together so yeah
let's see what we can do about about
bringing some people together I think
hmm I still I listened to your
conversation this guy I remember exactly
where I was in back in Bali and it was a
wonderful kind of smile inducing
conversation and one question for you
Tim is from out of that conversation
what insights emerged about the way the
way the conversation unfolded in fact
you would like to bring forth in to
these because it felt to me as if the
way that you were conversing felt
different in some way to a lot of the
kind of usual in TV formats and and I
wonder if there was anything that the
surface for you during that conversation
that you'd like to bring forward into
future well one thing that jumps out of
me which which did occur to me in that
conversation had also occurred to me in
some previous conversations with guy
offline as well as sort of a budding
insight over the course of
the many conversations I've recorded was
just that that was a hyper moment of
accepting when and and really feeling
and trusting when you're getting close
to the boundary of your vulnerability
and there's so much energy to be found
there that can be that that can be
transmuted into freedom when it's it's
like it's a heightened moment of tuning
in and there was something at the right
the beginning of that conversation that
that triggered that for me in such a you
know it might sound like a trivial way
but I made a comment about my hair and
actually growing up I genuinely did have
quite a lot of insecurities about my
hair I would wet it like 20 times a day
at school I'll just be shaking it around
because it just sorta freezing out and
and I I cut it myself and it was just a
disaster I didn't know what to do so I
was always wetting it it's just
ridiculous it's basically trenched all
day and I felt that that was that was
better than just letting it be what it
was and I made a comment about you know
I asked guy to introduce himself and he
just went he just basically didn't
answer that at all and just said
something about well what's calling me
to ask you right now is have you had a
haircut or something or is that your
real hair I was like yeah yeah it's my
real hair you know that I'm just sitting
here was but it kind of it put me on the
spot in that way it brought up a little
bit of a a trigger and that
vulnerability and I think guys a like a
genuine master of doing that right he
it's it's inviting someone to step into
just like it almost it it's not really
about the hair like it's for
get that it's like something else it's
just to the boundary of your
vulnerability in a way that allows you
to voluntarily extend it but there's a
real experience to that right and you
can't think there's a feeling that you
could collapse in the face of it but I
think a true master it gives you just
that challenge where you don't and I
think what comes after that is is a
certain freedom and a relaxation
you know this where you just shared Tim
I'm sensing a connection between what
Johnny shared and what you just shared
because now amidst the the dissolution
of so many trajectories people had
planned and had seen like their futures
unfolding in certain ways from from
small things like a graduation or a prom
to much larger tragedies I'm losing a
job or you know having a few lesson
years with your grandparents or your
parents or something like that there's
there's going to be a massive wave of
vulnerability that now people are like
in touch with and there may have been
that vulnerability subterranean for
quite some time but the salience of that
vulnerability is now really getting
cranked up and I hope I that there's an
opportunity for people to bring that
vulnerability with their loved ones
their their connections their families
in a way that tightens and strengthens
that social fabric where they now feel
as a consequence of this crisis closer
to those that they love and that's part
of you know there are a lot of gifts in
loss that aren't very often talked about
and that could be one of them as this
unfolds now not everyone has surrounding
community that's able to hold
vulnerability in that way but to create
the space for it to model it in some
degree I think is this is a beautiful
endeavor too
- mm yeah and the the image of the the
flame that we talked about earlier kind
of comes back in my mind and and I
wonder if the the gift that we're giving
in some ways through these conversations
and these spaces are is purely that it
is creating a container in which it is
safe and and people are given permission
explicit permission to waste and express
and feel into those vulnerabilities and
perhaps by doing so we're also giving
them permission to then go and create
spaces for their loved ones and their
family and that is how this the kind of
the flame will the flame will spread
yeah guys I'm feeling that it may be
to move towards closure here because
we're probably coming up for about an
hour on the recording and perhaps we
could continue i i'm not i'm not sure
about are there are there any closing
thoughts you have and i love for us to
stick around by the way and sort of
check in with each other after this but
joining are there any closing thoughts
you have to to share Mike there was
there's one thing the surfaced as you
were do describing that conversation guy
and and your hair and if that was I
found I'm not funny and I thought that
so that was great and what strikes me is
as we're talking about this and it feels
like there was a lot of gravitas to what
we're talking about and there is a a
deep sense of well seriousness about
everything that's happening and an open
question for me is how can that be held
also with a sense of with joy and and
delight and humor and and how can we how
can we walk into this as full spectrum
humans and feel both ends and for me it
feels like this is also a time for for
laughter and for poetry and for music
and for for all of those kind of
essential human expressions as well so
it's yeah that's just something that is
a life meaty and not getting too sucked
down into the the gravity of the
situation
hmm there's a real feel
for me like in you know discussing grief
and loss and and the gravity that you
just described there Johnny there is I
think the place to or like it's good to
like be rooted in that and not being
magical thinking la-la-land positivity
you know I'm just going to manifest the
world that I want without addressing
like the actual real challenges and
grave concerns that this moment is
forcing us to look at the buoyancy can
be accessed when we Fiat like we lost a
fixation we've had a fixed future that
we may have mapped out some of us that
is very clearly not going to transpire
now and there is a concentration of our
energy that was was like mapped on to
this this thing and now that has been
diffused but that does not mean that
that energy is is lost it's just been
whatever that and valuable meaningful
thing we had been holding on to that we
are seeing in the future and that energy
is now is a bit more gaseous and
amorphis and is up to us to figure out
what where do we want to string these
these pieces up on and you know how how
is it that we decide to generate meaning
now given that this is the state that
we're in the truth is your life has
always been co-authorship with your
context you haven't always had your hand
on the pen as much as you know staunch
individualism is is touted it's always
been an exchange in a dance and this is
a real severe waking up to that and so
given the ten strokes that life is
making what do we choose to create from
there how do we advance the plot and so
what might feel like a void of meaning
like oh it's empty or dark its soil
there's possibility there there's a lot
that can emerge and and that is there is
an intoxicating like sense of potential
when you feel
connected with that and so I just voiced
that as a pathway to the to the buoyancy
racking reckoning with the gravity of
this moment is very important as well
but you know the buoyancy is important
too so that that's feels like the
sufficiently like a closing remark yeah
brother yeah it does wow that was
beautiful
wow that was beautiful it has to be that
way otherwise the vibration is truncated
alright otherwise the movement isn't
isn't fully extending itself has to be
the depth and the levity yeah and I'm
watching that come back online
slowly but surely so here's to that and
thank you so much for for joining me
thank you for having me yeah this has
been